

Jorge León Salas

Canada Vancouver BC

Portfolio

Jorge León Salas

Software Engineer

PROFILE

I'm a Mexican computer scientist with a diploma on XR design and development.

I love being part of the entire process when it comes to creating, so I can always learn and/or teach new things. Also, to design solutions that take in consideration every possible point of view.

I enjoy trying and developing experiences in game engines in my free time and would like to focus on user experience, such as intuitiveness and accessibility.

SKILLS



EDUCATION

VR/AR Design and Development Vancouver Film School - Aug 2022

Computer Science Engineering Instituto Tecnologico y de Estudios Superiores de Monterrey - Dec 2020

Videogame design & programming introductory course Vancouver Film School - Jul 2019

EXPERIENCE

<u>Visions of Yesterday - Client project</u>

TTT Studios / Vancouver, BC / April 2022 - August 2022

I was the lead developer and project manager for a proof of concept, Unity based, VR experience, targeted to generate empathy on caregivers for people that have dementia. I did the back-end programming for a story based experience, and managed many of the interactions inside the engine. I was also in charge of the communication with the client and constant re planning, so that the team, that consisted of four people could successfully deliver the product within the time given.

Graduate QA Automation Engineer

Solera, Inc / Mexico City, Santa Fe / December 2020 – December 2021

I worked with an internal framework that was mostly based on Selenium and C#. Alongside my manager, we created the first project to use the latest framework, combined with a structure for test cases and great 00P practices, we provided a base project which eliminated the necessity to run the automation project manually and locally, decreased the run time from 3 hours to 30 minutes, added the possibility to schedule runs, and have everything automatically reported to TestRail.

Digital Innovation & Technology - IT Applications Intern Schneider Electric / Mexico City, Polanco / September 2019 - June 2020

I mostly developed and maintained web applications. I took part on the development from scratch of a process that eliminated the manual necessity for the annual verification of registered clients.

OTHER PROJECTS

Cyber Attack / Vancouver Film School / 2022

A VR based board and FPS game, where I took the role of game programmer for many interactions. It was developed as the final project on the VR/AR design and development course on Unreal Engine 5 with blueprints.